electude.com 2009-06-08

# Privacy statement - Electude

Electude B.V. is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our website. Information we collect from you is used to improve our site, provide you a better experience, respond to your questions and requests.

### Information collection

We collect two types of information on our website: 

  * Web server traffic information. This information is used to determine the number of visitors to our site, length of stay and sources of traffic. We collect aggregate data - or totals of those visiting from a domain - not information identifying individual users. We use this information to help improve our site and our service to you.
  * Personal information provided by you. We collect email addresses and other personal information only when you provide it to us. If you fill out a form or request information, we may collect your name, address, city, state, zip code, telephone number and email address. We use your personal data to provide goods and services to you. Personal information may also be collected for the purposes of improving our website content, marketing, as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research or other ancillary purposes. We do not sell, rent or share any information provided to us to third parties without your explicit consent. 

### Cookies

To enhance your experience with our site, our web pages may use "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive.  
Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us at our website. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.  
You can choose not to accept these cookies by setting your browser accordingly. However, not accepting cookies can mean that you will not be able to access some pages on our website.

© 2009 Electude B.V.
